[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Heidi, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Heidi", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "Happy wife, happy life.", "answer_tokens": ["Happy", "wife", ",", "happy", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "VB", "POS", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Why don't we leave your husband out of this for the time being?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "n't", "we", "leave", "your", "husband", "out", "of", "this", "for", "the", "time", "being", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Come on, let's do it.", "answer_tokens": ["Come", "on", ",", "let", "'s", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "You're quite bossy, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "quite", "bossy", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Do you always get your own way?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "always", "get", "your", "own", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "But you see you did it.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "you", "see", "you", "did", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "I mean, you boss him around?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "boss", "him", "around", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "He's big, but he's very gentle.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "big", ",", "but", "he", "'s", "very", "gentle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Do you feel lucky to have met Seal?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "to", "have", "met", "Seal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "Because it felt like the pair of you had been sort of searching for each other and then you collided, and you have this extraordinary life with hundreds of children and fabulously successful careers?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "felt", "like", "the", "pair", "of", "you", "had", "been", "sort", "of", "searching", "for", "each", "other", "and", "then", "you", "collided", ",", "and", "you", "have", "this", "extraordinary", "life", "with", "hundreds", "of", "children", "and", "fabulously", "successful", "careers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "Four.", "answer_tokens": ["Four", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Was it really?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "What were you both doing there?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "you", "both", "doing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "I was just visiting a friend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "just", "visiting", "a", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "You knew him, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "knew", "him", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I hadn't met him before.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "had", "n't", "met", "him", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "And did he know you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "did", "he", "know", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "So what happened next?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "happened", "next", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I told him to sit down, have a pizza with us.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "told", "him", "to", "sit", "down", ",", "have", "a", "pizza", "with", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Literally, like that?", "question_tokens": ["Literally", ",", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "And he hasn't got a clue you're Heidi Klum the supermodel?", "question_tokens": ["And", "he", "has", "n't", "got", "a", "clue", "you", "'re", "Heidi", "Klum", "the", "supermodel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi Klum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "He doesn't know, seriously?", "question_tokens": ["He", "does", "n't", "know", ",", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "So what happens then?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "happens", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "Then we met each other again, but always with friends.", "answer_tokens": ["Then", "we", "met", "each", "other", "again", ",", "but", "always", "with", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "It was pretty good?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "pretty", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "It went like this and normally we'd go and we just went like this.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "went", "like", "this", "and", "normally", "we", "'d", "go", "and", "we", "just", "went", "like", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "And who gripped who?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "gripped", "who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "We both gripped each other.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "both", "gripped", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "And what were you thinking in that second?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "in", "that", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I got really hot.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "really", "hot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Did you think this is the guy?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "this", "is", "the", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "I was like, oh, wow.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "like", ",", "oh", ",", "wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Had you kissed lots of frogs to get to this point?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "you", "kissed", "lots", "of", "frogs", "to", "get", "to", "this", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Otherwise, things just don't get done, do they?", "question_tokens": ["Otherwise", ",", "things", "just", "do", "n't", "get", "done", ",", "do", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "So you squeeze hands, and then you get married.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "you", "squeeze", "hands", ",", "and", "then", "you", "get", "married", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "He had an igloo built on a mountain?", "question_tokens": ["He", "had", "an", "igloo", "built", "on", "a", "mountain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Wait, what was the song?", "question_tokens": ["Wait", ",", "what", "was", "the", "song", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "He just made something up.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "just", "made", "something", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "How could any woman resist this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "could", "any", "woman", "resist", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 214, "question": "And what were his exact words of proposal?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "were", "his", "exact", "words", "of", "proposal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "\"Do you want to marry me?\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Do", "you", "want", "to", "marry", "me", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What did you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "I said yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "said", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Henry"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "And then what happened?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "And then nine months later Henry was born.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "then", "nine", "months", "later", "Henry", "was", "born", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "How do you be a mother to four children with everything else you do?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "be", "a", "mother", "to", "four", "children", "with", "everything", "else", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "You know, I don't know how that happened.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "that", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP"], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Are there any more planned?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "any", "more", "planned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "RBR", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "No, that's it", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "it"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Do you like working with him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "working", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "How do you keep this skinny figure that you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "keep", "this", "skinny", "figure", "that", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you started it would be nine seasons?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "when", "you", "started", "it", "would", "be", "nine", "seasons", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "No way.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "-- right?", "question_tokens": ["--", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Did I pronounce that right?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "I", "pronounce", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Was that always the dream for you?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "always", "the", "dream", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "You conquered the world of modeling, didn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "conquered", "the", "world", "of", "modeling", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "A little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "-- exciting moment for you?", "question_tokens": ["--", "exciting", "moment", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Every one and it still is, because everyone is a little step again.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "one", "and", "it", "still", "is", ",", "because", "everyone", "is", "a", "little", "step", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Not thin enough and too short?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "thin", "enough", "and", "too", "short", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "For this industry, yes, because the designers, such as him, they require the girls to be a certain weight, height and size.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "this", "industry", ",", "yes", ",", "because", "the", "designers", ",", "such", "as", "him", ",", "they", "require", "the", "girls", "to", "be", "a", "certain", "weight", ",", "height", "and", "size", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 416, "question": "And, also, it's dangerous sort of nonsense that he's starting, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", ",", "also", ",", "it", "'s", "dangerous", "sort", "of", "nonsense", "that", "he", "'s", "starting", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I mean, I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 424, "question": "If I don't, I go back to Germany and I do something else, you know?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "do", "n't", ",", "I", "go", "back", "to", "Germany", "and", "I", "do", "something", "else", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "I mean, there is a danger --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "there", "is", "a", "danger", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Any -- any scalpel at any stage?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "--", "any", "scalpel", "at", "any", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Would you ever?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "ever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I mean, I don't want to say never.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "want", "to", "say", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Who are you doing it for?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "you", "doing", "it", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 493, "question": "Is your great gift, if you like, the fact that you're secure in yourself, you're self-confident?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "your", "great", "gift", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "'re", "secure", "in", "yourself", ",", "you", "'re", "self-confident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "Yes, I have --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "have", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "You like making money, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "like", "making", "money", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "That, too.", "answer_tokens": ["That", ",", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Where did you get that from?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "get", "that", "from", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I don't know if I'm that smart at it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "'m", "that", "smart", "at", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "ORGAN: Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "That's true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'94"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "-NONE-", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "-- keen to do that?", "question_tokens": ["--", "keen", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I've been here since '94.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "here", "since", "'94", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "How do you think he's doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "That is a tough question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "a", "tough", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "-- how do the Germans all feel when you when you became an American?", "question_tokens": ["--", "how", "do", "the", "Germans", "all", "feel", "when", "you", "when", "you", "became", "an", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I still am a German, as well.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "still", "am", "a", "German", ",", "as", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 562, "question": "Oh, you are?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 563, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Did you ever stop being a German?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "stop", "being", "a", "German", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I have a dual citizenship.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "dual", "citizenship", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "What do you think of America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "I really like it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "like", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Modern -- in the -- in the modern era, in the last sort of 30, 40 years?", "question_tokens": ["Modern", "--", "in", "the", "--", "in", "the", "modern", "era", ",", "in", "the", "last", "sort", "of", "30", ",", "40", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "In Germany, definitely, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "Germany", ",", "definitely", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "What's next for the Heidi Klum Incorporated machine?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "next", "for", "the", "Heidi", "Klum", "Incorporated", "machine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "More designing.", "answer_tokens": ["More", "designing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Heidi Klum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "From the things -- yes, that I cook up.", "answer_tokens": ["From", "the", "things", "--", "yes", ",", "that", "I", "cook", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "-- to, any of them, to get into fashion, would you worry about it, given the experiences you've had?", "question_tokens": ["--", "to", ",", "any", "of", "them", ",", "to", "get", "into", "fashion", ",", "would", "you", "worry", "about", "it", ",", "given", "the", "experiences", "you", "'ve", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "I would not push them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "not", "push", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "-- a rock star like their dad?", "question_tokens": ["--", "a", "rock", "star", "like", "their", "dad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Well I -- I look forward to these kids growing up, actually, because they must -- they're going to look great and be very talented, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["Well", "I", "--", "I", "look", "forward", "to", "these", "kids", "growing", "up", ",", "actually", ",", "because", "they", "must", "--", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "look", "great", "and", "be", "very", "talented", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Oh, they're a lot of fun.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "they", "'re", "a", "lot", "of", "fun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "What's your proudest achievement, you personally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "proudest", "achievement", ",", "you", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Oh, my family for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "family", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "And then what?", "question_tokens": ["And", "then", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "And you come home to a guy who just gets on bended knee in igloos and sings you crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "you", "come", "home", "to", "a", "guy", "who", "just", "gets", "on", "bended", "knee", "in", "igloos", "and", "sings", "you", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'80s"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Who would've thought that to be 80s in Britain?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "'ve", "thought", "that", "to", "be", "80s", "in", "Britain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "We survived the '80s.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "survived", "the", "'80s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "But when you come to America now, how's it changed in all senses from when you first came out here?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "come", "to", "America", "now", ",", "how", "'s", "it", "changed", "in", "all", "senses", "from", "when", "you", "first", "came", "out", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "How was L.A. when we first came here, first?", "question_tokens": ["How", "was", "L.A.", "when", "we", "first", "came", "here", ",", "first", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Boring.", "answer_tokens": ["Boring", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["L.A."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andy Taylor", "Duran Duran"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "So how did you get kicked out?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "did", "you", "get", "kicked", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "Andy Taylor, who was a guitarist with Duran Duran, was standing on top of the hotel where there's a pool.", "answer_tokens": ["Andy", "Taylor", ",", "who", "was", "a", "guitarist", "with", "Duran", "Duran", ",", "was", "standing", "on", "top", "of", "the", "hotel", "where", "there", "'s", "a", "pool", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Modern bands just don't do this kind of thing, do they?", "question_tokens": ["Modern", "bands", "just", "do", "n't", "do", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", ",", "do", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "They haven't lived.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "n't", "lived", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 724, "question": "Really you're not a proper rock star, right?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "you", "'re", "not", "a", "proper", "rock", "star", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 725, "answer": "E BON: Bloody jordies.", "answer_tokens": ["E", "BON", ":", "Bloody", "jordies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "How are you finding the changing style of music?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "finding", "the", "changing", "style", "of", "music", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "Vinyl is here, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["Vinyl", "is", "here", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "How do you guys listen to music yourselves?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "guys", "listen", "to", "music", "yourselves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "Well, ideally, I listen to music like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "ideally", ",", "I", "listen", "to", "music", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Do all of you do?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "all", "of", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Why do you prefer it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "prefer", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "It's better quality.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "better", "quality", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 749, "question": "Vinyl is better, is it?", "question_tokens": ["Vinyl", "is", "better", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 750, "answer": "It's a better sound.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "better", "sound", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "Is it, really?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "It's a ritual, putting it on, getting it oust sleeve, making sure that there's no fluff on it, and putting it on and putting the needle on.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "ritual", ",", "putting", "it", "on", ",", "getting", "it", "oust", "sleeve", ",", "making", "sure", "that", "there", "'s", "no", "fluff", "on", "it", ",", "and", "putting", "it", "on", "and", "putting", "the", "needle", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "Are you guys on iTunes?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "guys", "on", "iTunes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "We are.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "Or is all the money now just, from as I hear it, from touring and merchandise?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "all", "the", "money", "now", "just", ",", "from", "as", "I", "hear", "it", ",", "from", "touring", "and", "merchandise", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "Well, obviously, there's been enormous problems with illegal downloads, which has affected the entire industry in a massive way.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "obviously", ",", "there", "'s", "been", "enormous", "problems", "with", "illegal", "downloads", ",", "which", "has", "affected", "the", "entire", "industry", "in", "a", "massive", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "How did you -- when you came on stage, how did you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "--", "when", "you", "came", "on", "stage", ",", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "Terrible.", "answer_tokens": ["Terrible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fiona", "Simon"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 835, "question": "Which way around was it?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "way", "around", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 836, "answer": "Well, actually, there was a middle person, Fiona, that Simon was living with.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "actually", ",", "there", "was", "a", "middle", "person", ",", "Fiona", ",", "that", "Simon", "was", "living", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 849, "question": "Or you never really crossed that barrier?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "you", "never", "really", "crossed", "that", "barrier", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 850, "answer": "It was something a little opportunistic about that, I think.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "something", "a", "little", "opportunistic", "about", "that", ",", "I", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 867, "question": "Did he really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 868, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBD", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 872, "question": "Or how did he revive the Duran magic, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "how", "did", "he", "revive", "the", "Duran", "magic", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 873, "answer": "Well, I think really what Mark did was focus our attention on what we're good at.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "really", "what", "Mark", "did", "was", "focus", "our", "attention", "on", "what", "we", "'re", "good", "at", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 877, "question": "Was it reminding you, as a fan, was it reminding you of what you're all really good at, or was it making you more adaptable to the modern market?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "reminding", "you", ",", "as", "a", "fan", ",", "was", "it", "reminding", "you", "of", "what", "you", "'re", "all", "really", "good", "at", ",", "or", "was", "it", "making", "you", "more", "adaptable", "to", "the", "modern", "market", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 878, "answer": "He said you don't have to try, you just have to do what you do, and that's what people want from you.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "said", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "try", ",", "you", "just", "have", "to", "do", "what", "you", "do", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "what", "people", "want", "from", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 886, "question": "When you see what happened to Amy, what do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "what", "happened", "to", "Amy", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 887, "answer": "Well, I think we were fortunate that we were a band, first of all, and that we always had each other.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "we", "were", "fortunate", "that", "we", "were", "a", "band", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "and", "that", "we", "always", "had", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Amy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 901, "question": "She got so thin, didn't she?", "question_tokens": ["She", "got", "so", "thin", ",", "did", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 902, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "Did you not?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 920, "question": "Are these old fans of yours who've come with you or do you have a new breed?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "these", "old", "fans", "of", "yours", "who", "'ve", "come", "with", "you", "or", "do", "you", "have", "a", "new", "breed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 921, "answer": "A mix.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "mix", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 970, "question": "We're never speaking again?", "question_tokens": ["We", "'re", "never", "speaking", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 971, "answer": "I think being a band goes beyond friendship, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "being", "a", "band", "goes", "beyond", "friendship", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "VBG", "CC", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 983, "question": "Do you have a genuine ambition, or is it to keep going?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "genuine", "ambition", ",", "or", "is", "it", "to", "keep", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 984, "answer": "I think the keeping going and to create a body of work is one of the big ambitions.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "keeping", "going", "and", "to", "create", "a", "body", "of", "work", "is", "one", "of", "the", "big", "ambitions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 997, "question": "Is it more of a primitive, because I would imagine you would be the first in that kind of stuff?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "more", "of", "a", "primitive", ",", "because", "I", "would", "imagine", "you", "would", "be", "the", "first", "in", "that", "kind", "of", "stuff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 998, "answer": "I like the idea of it, but I think, one, it is very time consuming.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "the", "idea", "of", "it", ",", "but", "I", "think", ",", "one", ",", "it", "is", "very", "time", "consuming", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Coachella"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 1004, "question": "Would you be in agreement you think?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "be", "in", "agreement", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1005, "answer": "Well, you know, Coachella was great.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Coachella", "was", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 1011, "question": "Was it the best ever?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "the", "best", "ever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1012, "answer": "I think to that point --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "to", "that", "point", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 1013, "question": "ORGAN: Even at the height of the mania?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Even", "at", "the", "height", "of", "the", "mania", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1014, "answer": "You can't just pick one.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "just", "pick", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Cuccurullo"]}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1022, "question": "In Duran Duran history?", "question_tokens": ["In", "Duran", "Duran", "history", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1023, "answer": "Well, the Warren Cuccurullo.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "Warren", "Cuccurullo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 1027, "question": "When was that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1028, "answer": "Pink Flamingos.", "answer_tokens": ["Pink", "Flamingos", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1029, "question": "Pink Flamingo?", "question_tokens": ["Pink", "Flamingo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 1030, "answer": "The groom wore more makeup than the bride.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "groom", "wore", "more", "makeup", "than", "the", "bride", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1037, "question": "I mean, you do for this show, but do you normally?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "do", "for", "this", "show", ",", "but", "do", "you", "normally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1038, "answer": "It's a tattoo.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "tattoo", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 1039, "question": "When you're going out, do you still get the old gear on?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "going", "out", ",", "do", "you", "still", "get", "the", "old", "gear", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1040, "answer": "If I feel like it, you never know.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "feel", "like", "it", ",", "you", "never", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 1043, "question": "Simon, do you?", "question_tokens": ["Simon", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1044, "answer": "If I feel I need it, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "feel", "I", "need", "it", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 1051, "question": "Who is the best other singer you have ever seen live?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "best", "other", "singer", "you", "have", "ever", "seen", "live", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 1052, "answer": "Well, I love --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "love", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111028pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 1061, "question": "It's all about now, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "about", "now", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1062, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]